I want you to open your heart.
You have to be free from any torture of the enemy of your soul.
You know how the enemy tortures us -
by bringing the words of anxiety, sadness, depression, worrying about the future.
That kind of language going on in your heart is enemy's weapon to torture you.
Reject any torture from the enemy of your soul.
Anxious, sad, depressed, worry about your future, downcast.
These are enemy's what? - Torture.
Begin to reject it right now. Reject it.
Begin to reject any torture from the enemy of your soul.
Any torture - those words that are going through your heart to torture your heart, torture you,
worry about your future - reject it, in the name of Jesus and be free!
Leave it for God!
Reject any torture from the enemy of your soul -
anxiety, sadness, doubt, worry about the future.
With God, all things are possible.
Stop worrying! Stop worrying about your healing!
Stop worrying about your blessing .
Stop worrying about your future!
Stop worrying about your situation. In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
No man is without limitation. Tell your neighbour.
[No man is without limitation.]
I can't hear you.
When you say, "Eh hen, T.B. Joshua! What is T.B. Joshua's limitation?"
It's not possible for T.B. Joshua to be praying for people and at the same time being prayed for.
I'm here praying and you are receiving my prayer.
Why can't I be here and be there?
That is my limitation.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I repeat again.
As I'm here now praying for you, "Be healed!",
can I also be there receiving that healing?
Eh hen! That is my limitation.
If I can be here praying and at the same time be there, receiving that blessing,
it means I don't have limitation.
So it means, where you are strong, I'm weak; where you are weak, I'm strong.
So when you know that no man is without limitation -
your limitation could be physical, spiritual, financial, emotional.
Just mention it.
What is your limitation?
This is why, before you come to the Lord, you have to rebuke any torture from the enemy of your soul.
Those tortures are from the enemy of your soul to make you think of your limitation.
Open your lips once again.
Before you begin to pray, even in your house, you have to get rid of torture from the enemy;
those things that make you worry.
As if you and God, God does not need you to do that.
Open your lips and begin to reject it right now - any torture from the enemy of your soul.
Depression, worry about now and the future is enemy torture.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
"How will I pay my debt?" - these are enemy torture.
Reject it!
in the name of Jesus!
You don't need to worry. Leave it for God. Leave it for Him.
The moment you start leaving it for God, you start receiving breakthrough.
Leave it for God!
You need a free spirit; you don't need a worry spirit.
When your spirit is worried, you cannot contact God.
You just have to be calm.
In Jesus Christ's name.
Right now, let us restore our sight.
Our human eyes can be blind to His act of mercy.
Our human eyes can be blind to His act of healing, act of salvation, act of blessing.
Lord Jesus, restore our sight to see His mercy.
Restore our sight to see His healing.
Restore our sight to see His blessing.
Restore our sight to see His salvation.
When our eyes are restored, we will feel His touch.
Somebody touched me
Somebody touched my soul
When I was praying
Praying to my Father
Somebody touched my soul
When our eyes are restored, you will feel His touch;
you will hear Him say, "You are healed!";
you will hear Him say, "You are blessed!";
you will hear Him say, "You are saved!"
Open your lips now and pray to the Lord - restore my sight, Lord.
My human eyes can be blind to Your act of mercy.
My human eyes can be blind to Your act of salvation.
My human eyes can be blind to Your act of healing.
Lord Jesus, restore my sight to see Your healing.
Restore my sight to see Your salvation.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Say, my dominion is in Christ Jesus.
I command you, you satan, you evil spirit - out!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Anointing is in the house.
See the evidence right now on your screen.
People are manifesting - the evil spirits in them.
And those who have taken poison from the table of the enemy
have begun to come out to vomit out the poison from their system.
We can see what is happening right now with that man.
There is an evil spirit in him that is manifesting.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Every sickness, disease, wherever it is located in your system,
every sickness, infirmity, wherever it is located in your blood -
I command them out in the name of Jesus!
Command them out!
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Watch your screen and see people vomiting out poisonous substances from their system
in different parts of the church right now.
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Demons have no hiding place in the arena of liberty.
They are being exposed in the lives of the people.
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
By your dominion in Christ Jesus -
stand by your dominion and tell that sickness in your system, blood, organs to leave you,
in the name of Jesus!
Say, "Leave me, in the name of Jesus!"
Prayer!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Continue to watch your screen.
Anywhere you are, viewers out there, distance is not a barrier.
They are vomiting out...
In that mighty name of Jesus Christ!
The name Jesus is a Searcher - He will search wherever that sickness is located.
I want you to be with me and agree with me - when Jesus says, "Yes", no one can say, "No".
That your sickness, that your disease - it is time. Say, "Time off!"
Right now, time off, in the name of Jesus!
I say, "Leave my people!"
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Are you ready to leave that sickness?
Sickness is ready to leave you.
Wherever it is located - I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Out, in the name of Jesus!
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
That fibroid - out, in the name of Jesus!
That cancer - out, in the name of Jesus!
That diabetes - out, in the name of Jesus!
Hypertension - out, in the name of Jesus!
Blood pressure - out, in the name of Jesus!
Liver problem - out, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Whatever medium satan might have used to connect you to himself -
to connect your career to himself, to connect your finances to himself -
begin to break the medium!
Break the chain!
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Listen!
Whatever satan might have used to connect your career to himself -
when one's career is connected to evil spirit, failure, worry, depression -
whatever satan might have used - he always uses our worries, challenges, situation -
whatever satan might have used, whatever medium,
whatever chain satan might have used to connect you,
I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Your health - be released, in the name of Jesus!
I release your health, in the name of Jesus!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
That career - be released, in the name of Jesus!
That business - be released, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Say to your neighbour, "Someone is releasing me in the Person of the Holy Ghost".
Holy Ghost!
Someone is releasing me in the Person of the Holy Ghost.
Someone is releasing me.
Someone is releasing my health.
Someone is releasing my business.
Someone is releasing my career.
Someone is releasing my future.
Join Him - give Him a chance, give Him an opportunity to release you.
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus!
I can see you being released.
I can see your career being released.
I can see your finances being released.
I can see your business being released.
I can see your marriage being released.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Where the Spirit of the Lord is, there is freedom.
In Jesus Christ's name.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I see you being released.
Begin to rejoice in your release.
This is a new dawn. Rejoice!
I can feel it!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I can sense it. I can sense your release.
In Jesus Christ's name.
Cover yourself with the blood of Jesus. The way out has come!
Cover yourself with the blood of Jesus. The way out for you has come!
Begin to cover yourself with the blood of Jesus. The way out for me has come!
Begin to cover yourself with the blood of Jesus. The way out for you has come!
The way out for your business has come.
The way out for your career has come.
The way out for your finances has come.
I cover myself with the blood of Jesus.
TT: Monica Asefa 16/07/18
RV: Mel Flowers 29/07/2018